<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<exhibition title="Far From Home">
     <artwork id="1">
        <artist>Pieter Claesz</artist>
        <title>Breakfast Piece</title>
        <date>1636</date>
        <medium>Oil on panel</medium>
        <type>Painting</type>
        <dimensions>49cmx36cm</dimensions>
        <origin>Northern Netherlands</origin>
        <location>Rotterdam</location>
        <owner>Museum Boijmans van Beuningen</owner>
        <genre>Still life</genre>
        <label>This panel is a masterpiece from Pieter Claesz' monochrome period. 
        The soft light and finely tuned colour palette in this balanced composition 
        produces an atmosphere of calm. With its great simplicity, with only a single
        glass of beer, a knife, a herring, a bread and the cracked shell of a single hazelnut, 
        this panel sings the praises of 'our daily bread'.</objectlabel>
        <theme>Around the Kitchen Table</theme>
        <narrative>
            <narrativeName></narrativeName>
            <narrativeDescription></narrativeDescription>
        <narrative>
    </artwork>

    <artwork id="2">
        <artist>Edward Hopper</artist>
        <title>Nighthawks</title>
        <date>1942</date>
        <medium>Oil on canvas</medium>
        <type>Painting</type>
        <dimensions>84.1cmx152.4cm</dimensions>
        <origin>United States</origin>
        <location>Chicago</location>
        <owner>Art Institute Chicago</owner>
        <genre>Realism</genre>
        <description>Hopper's urban tableau captures metropolitan solitude through four 
        isolated figures within a glowing nocturnal refuge. The artist constructs a 
        paradox—physical proximity yet emotional distance—where shared space cannot bridge 
        human disconnection. This precisely composed scene transforms an ordinary diner 
        into theater, questioning whether true belonging exists within the modern 
        cityscape's anonymous embrace.</description>
    </artwork>

    <artwork id="3">
        <artist>Yinka Shonibare CBE</artist>
        <title>Refugee Astronaut VIII</title>
        <date>2024</date>
        <medium>Fibreglass mannequin, Dutch wax printed cotton textile, net, possessions, astronaut helmet, moon boots and steel baseplate</medium>
        <genre>Contemporary sculpture</genre>
        <description>Shonibare's life-sized astronaut figure, adorned in vibrant "African" 
        fabric and carrying worldly possessions, embodies contemporary displacement and 
        environmental crisis. This powerful sculpture envisions space as humanity's ultimate
         refuge, confronting viewers with urgent questions about climate change, migration, 
         and the search for sanctuary in an uncertain future.</description>
    </artwork>

    <artwork id="4">
        <artist>Michel Anguier</artist>
        <title>The Flood</title>
        <date>1648-1649</date>
        <medium>Stone relief</medium>
        <genre>Religious/Historical relief</genre>
        <description>Anguier's dramatic relief depicts humanity's ultimate displacement—the 
        biblical deluge that destroys all earthly homes. Figures cling desperately to 
        remnants of their world as waters rise, embodying the universal fear of losing 
        everything familiar. This baroque masterpiece transforms catastrophic homelessness 
        into a meditation on survival and divine judgment.</description>
    </artwork>

    <artwork id="5">
        <artist>Mathilde Mupe</artist>
        <title>The Stone Age Computer</title>
        <date>1993</date>
        <medium>Mixed media/Digital art</medium>
        <genre>Conceptual/Digital art</genre>
        <description>This conceptual work bridges ancient and digital realms, 
        suggesting technology as both connector and alienator from authentic human 
        experience. The primitive computer metaphor explores how modern digital 
        tools can simult </description>
    </artwork>
</exhibition>



